iqlikmovies.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy :: iQlik Movies

#### Identity of iQlikmovies

The entertainment website of Dream Axiz Inc. is at https://www.iqlikmovies.com and we operates in the area of Indian Film Industry related news only. 

This page informs you of our privacy & cookie policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. 

We encourage you to read the Privacy Notice carefully. By choosing to access or use the Site and Services, you agree to these Terms. 

If there are any questions regarding this Policy you can contact DREAM AXIZ using details below (Data Controller details): 

**Company Name:** DREAM AXIZ SOFTWARE PRIVATE LIMITED   
**Company Address:** 6th Floor, SLN Terminus Building, Beside Botanical Garden, Gachibowli, Hyderabad, Telangana, 500032.  
**Country:** India  
**Company Registration Number:** U72200AP2012PTC082947   
**Contact Mail Id:** iqlikmovies@gmail.com  
**Contact Phone No:** +91 40 65643456

#### Type of Data Collected

We follow EU's General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR") which defines personal data as: "...any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ('data subject'); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person". When we use terms "personal data" or "personal information", we mean exactly that. 

**Personal Data:** While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: 

  * Email address
  * First name and last name
  * Phone number
  * Tax code, address, city, zip code, state country
  * Cookies and Usage Data

Personal data is not just created by a user's interactions with your site. Personal data is also generated from technical processes such as contact forms, comments, cookies, analytics, and third party embeds. 

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. 

**Usage Data:** We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data"). 

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

**Location Data:** We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission to do so ("Location Data"). We use this data to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service. 

You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any time, through your device settings. 

**Tracking Cookies Data:** We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information. 

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. 

**Examples of Cookies we use:**   
Session Cookies: We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.  
Preference Cookies: We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.  
Security Cookies: We use Security Cookies for security purposes. 

#### HOW & Why WE USE COOKIES?

The types of first and third-party cookies served through our Site and the purposes they perform are described in further detail below: 

**Advertising:** We may utilize cookies to serve you relevant ads on our platform. Also, the third parties we work with may set certain cookies to gauge your interest and serve ads either on our site or some other sites. 

**Security:** To ensure the security of our systems, we may utilize cookies to only allow valid visitors and users to access our site and services. 

**Authentication:** Cookies are used to authenticate customers to provide them access to the service. 

**Analytics:** Cookies may also be used to track the actions and properties of the visitors. 

**Couponing/Offers:** Cookies may be used to provide discounts and other offers to customers. 

#### Data Retention

**DREAM AXIZ** will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. 

We will maintain your information for eighteen months after that relationship ends, unless you request that we delete your information prior to the expiration of that period, which you may do at any time by mailing us or via visiting our contact us page. Except as required under the law, your request will be honored within 30 days. 

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. 

If you have any questions about reviewing, modifying, deleting data or request for 'do no contact' list your account information, you can contact us directly at iqlikmovies@gmail.com.

#### Data Transfer & Sharing

Please refer the "Service Providers Information" below for crucial Data Processors details to whom your data may get transfer. 

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law, enforce or apply Our Terms and other agreements, or protect the rights, property, or safety of Dream Axiz, Our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. However, at no point does this include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

**DREAM AXIZ** will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

#### Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. DREAM AXIZ aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. 

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. 

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights: 

  * **The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.** Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you.
  * **The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  * **The right of restriction.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  * **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where DREAM AXIZ relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. 

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA). 

#### Data Protection 

We take reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect unauthorized access, alteration or destruction of data located on and collected by our Service. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Service and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. We exercise reasonable care to protect your non-public personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your non-public personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us while it is in transit. Once we receive your personal information, we maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect it. If a data breach occurs, we will notify you and the proper EEA authority (if required) within 72 hours (if reasonably feasible). If we are unable to notify the proper EEA authority within 72 hours, our notice will be accompanied by reasons for the delay. 

Please note that when you post information on blogs, public forums or similar functions in the Site, or when you interact with the Services through social networking sites (depending on your privacy settings), social media plug-ins or similar applications, this information could be seen by anyone on the internet. Therefore, we cannot prevent further use of this information. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social networking sites. For more information about how you can customize your privacy settings and how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies and terms of use. 

#### Related to data breach procedures

Compromise of information: In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, DREAM AXIZ will take reasonable steps (such as internal reporting systems, contact mechanisms, or bug bounties) to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and GDPR regulations. 

#### Do No Track Settings & Cookies Option

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. 

You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. Most browsers allow control of cookies through the browser settings feature. However, by disallowing of cookies you may restrict your user experience since it may no longer be customized to you. 

If you do not want to receive cookies you can change your browser settings on your device that you use to access our services. If you use our services without changing the settings on your device, we will assume that you are accepting to use the cookies that reference to this policy. Most browsers provide the functionality to review and delete cookies, however please note that our site will not work properly without cookies. 

To find out more about cookies visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/, or www.aboutcookies.org. 

#### Service Providers Information (Data Processors details)

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

We do it to provide you with analytics information and to improve our product and services. To do analytics we use certain analytics providers, which are comply with GDPR requirements. The range of our analytic providers together with links to their privacy policies are listed below. The list will be updated as new providers are added. 

Also see "Why we use your data" in the above. DREAM AXIZ uses third parties to track user statistics like: 

**Google Analytics & other Google integration:** Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. 

To see how Google uses your information, review How Google uses data when you use Google's partners' sites or apps. For more info related to DPA of Google Analytics you may visit https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/dpa/dataprocessingamendment_20160909.html. For Google Ads Privacy, you may visit here at https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads. 

Also you may refer https://policies.google.com/privacy for a complete policy detailing. 

**Facebook Ads -** All the details related to Facebook conversions are here at https://www.facebook.com/policies/ads/ and the policy here at https://www.facebook.com/legal/FB_Work_Privacy. 

**YouTube -** Privacy guidelines could be seen here at https://www.youtube.com/yt/about/policies. 

**Alexa:** Privacy policy of Alexa could be found here at https://www.alexa.com/help/privacy. 

**Yahoo Small Business:** Privacy policy is visible here at https://www.yahoosmallbusiness.com/privacy-policy. 

**Statcounter -** Privacy policy update could be seen here at https://statcounter.com/about/legal/ 

**Quantcast-** Here is the policy page at https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/. 

**Lotame-** Privacy policy is here at https://www.lotame.com/about-lotame/privacy/lotames-products-services-privacy-policy/. 

**Matomo-** Here is the policy page at https://matomo.org/privacy-policy/. 

**ComScore-** Privacy policy is at https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy. 

**Clicky-** Here is the privacy policy of Clicky at https://clicky.com/terms/privacy. 

**Cloudfare-** Privacy policy is here at https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/. 

**Comodo-** Privacy policy is here at https://ssl.comodo.com/privacy-policy.php. 

**AppNexus-** Privacy policy is here at https://www.appnexus.com/platform-privacy-policy. 

**Izooto-** Izooto Browser push notification could be seen here at https://www.izooto.com/privacy-policy. 

**Mediamath-** Privacy policy is here at http://www.mediamath.com/privacy-policy/. 

**AddThis-** Privacy policy is visible here at http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/. 

**Amazon-** The privacy update could be visible here at https://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010. 

#### Third Party External Links

The Site includes third party advertising and links to other Sites. These third party sites and advertisers, or internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send the advertisements that appear on the Site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your internet protocol address when this happens. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third party sites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

#### Children's Privacy Protection

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

  * By visiting our contact us page https://www.iqlikmovies.com/contactus
  * Or by direct mail at iqlikmovies@gmail.com

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. 

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

This privacy policy was last modified on 24th May 2018
